Inventory of the Eric Chenoweth papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Centers for Pluralism, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 28: 7)
  Includes grant proposal, agreement, and correspondence with financial reports.
- Centers for Pluralism quarterly report, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 28: 8)
- Centers for Pluralism, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 28: 9)
  Includes subgrantee agreements and reports.
- Backup floppy computer disks in Word Perfect 5.1 of IDEE-NED grant files plus database, 1994 (Box-folder 29: 1)
- CLOSED (Boxes 30-37)
- Centers for Anti-War Action (Yugoslavia) grant agreement, correspondence, budgets, notes, etc., 1993-1995 (Box-folder 38: 1)
- Balkan media (Romania and Croatia), subrecipients: local independent media, grant agreement, correspondence, reports, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 38: 2)
- Cuba, NED grants, final report, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 38: 3)
  Activities included 2 trips, training of Corriente Civico, development of publications ( Los Caminos). Original proposal/final report.
- Cuba, arrest of Irena Lasota in Cuba, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 38: 4)
- NED grant, Students Union of Serbia/Leskovac Human Rights Committee, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 38: 5)
  Includes grant agreement and correspondence.
- NED grant, IDEE quarterly financial reports, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 38: 6)
- NED grant, IDEE quarterly narrative reports, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 38: 7)
- NED grant, Leskovac Human Rights Committee, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 38: 8)
- NED grant, Students Union of Serbia (SUS) grant agreement/correspondence, SUS accounting questionnaire (model for NED practices), 1999-2000 (Box-folder 38: 9)
- NED grant, SUS, quarterly reports, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 38: 10)
  SUS ongoing correspondence/publication examples.
- NED grant, SUS, general support of SUS, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 39: 1)
  Includes grant agreement/correspondence/extension.
- IDEE quarterly reports, SUS ongoing correspondence/Free Serbia proposal, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 39: 2)
- Chechnya, humanitarian aid, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 39: 3)
  Includes grant agreement/correspondence/reports, IDEE quarterly reports, and SUS correspondence.
- NED grant, SUS, general support of SUS, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 39: 4)
- Chechnya, reports and supporting materials, photos, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 39: 5)
- Centers for Pluralism newsletter, Nos. 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 40: 1)
- Centers for Pluralism newsletter, Nos. 7, 8, 9, 10, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 40: 2)
- Centers for Pluralism newsletter, Nos. 11, 12, 13, 14, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 40: 3)
- Centers for Pluralism newsletter, Nos.15, 16, 17, 18, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 40: 4)
- Centers for Pluralism newsletter, Nos. 19, 20, 21, 22, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 40: 5)
- Centers for Pluralism newsletter, Nos. 23, 24 [duplicate], 25, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 40: 6)
- Centers for Pluralism newsletter, Nos. 25, 26 [duplicate], 27, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 41: 1)
- Centers for Pluralism newsletter, Nos. 27, 28, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 41: 2)
- Azeri language, Centers for Pluralism newsletter, Nos. 3, 4, 6, 7, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 41: 3)
- Azeri language, Centers for Pluralism, III Sektor, Nos. 2/2003 and 3/2004, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 41: 4)
- Russian language, Centry Pluralizma, Nos. 3, 4/1997 and 9/1999 [duplicate], 1997-1999 (Box-folder 41: 5)
- Russian language, Centry Pluralizma, Nos. 5, 12, 13, 14, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 41: 6)
- Russian language, Centry Pluralizma, Nos. 15 [duplicate], 16, 18, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 41: 7)
- Ukrainian language, Centriw Pluralizmu, Nos. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 42: 1)
- Ukrainian language, Centriw Pluralizmu, Nos. 6, 7, 8, 10, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 42: 2)
- National Forum Foundation grant, trainers' directory for NGOs in CEE, subgrant of Democracy Networking Program, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 42: 3)
- National Forum Foundation, trainers' directory, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 42: 4)
- Open Society Foundation, former Yugoslavia (Serbia), independent media project, 1996 (Box-folder 42: 5)
- United States Institute of Peace, Support for Post-communism and Nationalism Symposia and Uncaptive Minds support, for Moscow, Kiyv, Sofia, and Tracoscan Symposia, 1996 (Box-folder 42: 6)
- Smith-Richardson Grant, Support for Post-communism and Nationalism Symposia and Uncaptive Minds support, for Moscow, Kyiv, Sofia,and Trakoscan Symposia, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 43: 1)
- German Marshall Fund, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 43: 2)
- German Marshall Fund, journalist study tour, binder for participants, 1998 (Box-folder 43: 3)
- Freedom House (FH), Cuba Democracy project subgrant, grant agreement, FH project description, 1999 (Box-folder 44: 1)
- Freedom House, Cuba Democracy project subgrant, democracy pamphlets 1, 1999 (Box-folder 44: 2)
- Freedom House, Cuba Democracy project subgrant, democracy pamphlets 2, English language text, 1999 (Box-folder 44: 3)
- Directorio Revolucianario Cubano, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 44: 4)
  General files/cooperation between organizations; conference notes.
- Freedom House, Strengthening Human Rights in Bosnia and Hercegovina, Croatia, Serbia project, 1999 (Box-folder 44: 5)
- Freedom House, Local Democratic Governance Program in Eastern Europe, 1999 (Box-folder 44: 6)
- Smith Richardson Foundation grant for American Committee on Chechnya, 2000 (Box-folder 45: 1)
- American Committee on Chechnya activity files, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 45: 2)
  Appeal, membership, protests, Chechnya Working Group, web page, development of dispatches from Chechnya, etc.
- Crimean Tatars, IDEE, organized trip of Mustafa Dzhemilev to U.S., 1996 (Box-folder 46: 1)
- Open Society Foundation, Azerbaijan democratization program, 1998 (Box-folder 46: 2)
  Regarding independent media, civil society, democratic coalitions, and election monitoring.
- Open Society Foundation, Azerbaijan democratization program, 1999 (Box-folder 46: 3)
  Regarding independent media, civil society, democratic coalitions, election monitoring.
- Open Society Foundation, Azerbaijan, IDEE reports, 1999 (Box-folder 46: 4)
- International Foundation for Electoral Systems (IFES), elections in Azerbaijan, election monitoring program for presidential elections, 2003 (Box-folder 47: 1)
  Subfolders: official correspondence, grant agreement, final reports, final statement, list of observers, official press, final expenditures, subgrant.
- United States Institute for Peace, Central Asia, Tashkent training program, 2003 (Box-folder 48: 1)
- Open Society Foundation - Paris, Belarus election monitoring program, 2004 (Box-folder 48: 2)
  Includes grant proposal and agreement.
- Open Society Foundation - Paris (cont'd), initial and final report of IDEE and election observers, 2004 (Box-folder 48: 3)
- Open Society Foundation - Paris (cont'd), initial and final reports of observers, 2004 (Box-folder 48: 4)
  Comprised of backup materials.
- Belarus background, 2004-2007 (Box-folder 48: 5)
- Open Society Foundation, networking, civil activists in Uzbekistan, 2004-2007 (Box-folder 48: 6)
- Open Society Foundation, Uzbekistan, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 48: 7)
  Includes grant agreement, initial report and materials, and final report.
- USAID grant, Yugoslavia, in support of democracy program in Yugoslavia, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 49: 1)
  Includes original proposal, revised proposal, correspondence, USAID registration and other requirements, cooperative agreement with attachments, and working plan.
- OFAC correspondence re sanctions, waiver, confiscated wire, 1998 (Box-folder 49: 2)
- Yugoslavia, IDEE quarterly narrative and financial reports, 1997 (Box-folder 49: 3)
- Yugoslavia, indirect cost agreement, 1997 (Box-folder 49: 4)
- Civic Initiative quarterly and events reports, NGO training, Tim TRI, town halls, democracy seminars, 1998 (Box-folder 49: 5)
- Yugoslavia, trip file, Belgrad, 1997 April 22-26 (Box-folder 50: 1)
- Yugoslavia, trip file, notes and report, 1999 January (Box-folder 50: 2)
- Yugoslavia, 1998 (Box-folder 50: 3)
  Comprised of general news and articles.
- USAID grant, Yugoslavia, Breaking Barriers, Building Bridges, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 50: 4)
  Continuation grant for Civic Bridges (Serbia, Montenegro and Kosovo), initial and final proposal/memoranda, correspondence, cooperative agreement with attachments, working plan.
- Yugoslavia, financial status reports, Office of Procurement, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 50: 5)
  Includes correspondence and documents.
- IDEE monthly activity reports to USAID, 2000 (Box-folder 50: 6)
- Yugoslavia, civic initiatives activity reports, 2000 (Box-folder 50: 7)
- Yugoslavia, Civic Bridges, internship and volunteer program, 1999 (Box-folder 50: 8)
- CI/Yugoslavia action, NGO/media proposals, USAID Serbia coordination meeting, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 51: 1)
  Civic Initiatives: Small Grants Competition, Third NGO Assembly.
- Chronological file, Breaking Barriers Building Bridges (BBBB), correspondence/faxes, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 51: 2)
  Including during wartime.
- Chronological file, Civic Bridges, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 51: 3)
- Chronological file, Civic Bridges, 2000 April - October (Box-folder 51: 4)
- Elections, 2000 (general), Vojvodina Parliament (Box-folder 52: 1)
- Yugoslavia, European Movement of Serbia, 1999 (Box-folder 52: 2)
- Yogoslavia, Nezavisnost - Independent Trade Union, 2000 (Box-folder 52: 3)
- Balkan Community Initiatives Foundation (Hyatt) and other outside initiatives, 2000 (Box-folder 52: 4)
- Civic Resistance Movement, case of Maki, 1999 (Box-folder 52: 5)
- Yugoslavia Action Group (wartime), 1997-1999 (Box-folder 52: 6)
- USAID NGO sustainability indexes for Serbia, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 52: 7)
  Conducted by Civic Initiatives.
- Yugoslavia, trip notes, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 52: 8)
- USAID grant, Civic Bridges, Serbia, Kosova, and Montenegro, NGO law/actions, elections/polling and projects, German Marshall Fund coordination meetings and lessons, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 53: 1)
- Izlaz 2000 preliminary report (Box-folder 53: 2)
- Izlaz 2000 campaign, publications/photos (Box-folder 53: 3)
- AID2 - Kosova, Kosova Action for Civic Initiatives grant files, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 53: 4)
- Trips to Kosovo, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 53: 5)
- Kosova, chronological file/ work records, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 53: 6)
- Kosova, SBASHK, Kosova Action for Civic Initiatives (KOHA Foundation), 1999 (Box-folder 54: 1)
- AID2 - Montenegro, chronological file, CEDEM grant, program files, 2000 (Box-folder 54: 2)
- Backup materials (publications), 1999-2000 (Box-folder 54: 3)
- USAID grant, Serbia, Civic Bridges, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 54: 4)
  Includes proposals, correspondence, and award.
- Serbia, request for obligation, financial reports, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 54: 5)
- IDEE quarterly reports, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 54: 6)
- CI quarterly reports and work files, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 54: 7)
- Civic Bridges, AID3 formal close out files, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 55: 1)
- Yugoslavia Lawyers' Committee for Human Rights (YUCOM), 1999-2000 (Box-folder 55: 2)
- General file, TV VINS/NUNS, 2000 October (Box-folder 55: 3)
- Free Serbia grant files, 2001 (Box-folder 55: 4)
- 4th NGO Assembly, 2001 November (Box-folder 55: 5)
- NGO proposals, small grants competition, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 55: 6)
- Trip files, February, May, December, memo for the future, 2000 (Box-folder 55: 7)
  Result of October 26-31 meetings with Eric Chenoweth and Irena Lasota.
- Publications, 1994 (Box-folder 56: 1)
  Republicanism by Nebojsa Popov (in Cyrillic); Democratic Forums (in Cyrillic); Mali Recnik Pjmova O Parlamentarizmu by Marijana Pajvancic (duplicate); Recnik Demokratije by Zoran Stojilkovic.
- Publications, 2000 (Box-folder 56: 2)
  Demokratski Politicki Sistemi by Jakub Karpinski; Konflikti i Politika by Jakub Karpinski; Sidikati u Evropi by Darko Marinkovic; Trzisna Demokratija by Miroslav Prokopijevic, Amnesty Campaign - YUCOM.
- Publications of Civic Initiatives, Mreza, 1-34, 2000 (Box-folder 56: 3)
- Publications, Izlaz 2000, preliminary report, Civic Initiatives, "Exit 2000, Becoming a Citizen," (Box-folder 56: 4)
- VHS tapes, TV VINS, democracy programs, 2001 (Box-folder 57: 1)
- SVE O Upravljanju by Sandy Adirondack, 2001 (Box-folder 58: 1)
- Challenges of Normal Life, 4th NGO Assembly, 2001 December 15-18 (Box-folder 58: 2)
  Includes five VHS tapes, TV VINS, democracy programs.
- USIA/ECA Caucasus programs, Women in the Caucasus (WIC 1), 1999-2000 (Box-folder 59: 1)
  Includes grant agreement/proposal.
- WIC 1 correspondence with USIA, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 59: 2)
- IDEE interim and final reports with attachments, 2000 (Box-folder 59: 3)
- Financial status reports, 2000 (Box-folder 59: 4)
- Azerbaijan NGO partner agreement, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 59: 5)
- Armenia NGO partner agreement, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 59: 6)
- Georgia NGO partner agreement, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 59: 7)
- "Working Together: Networking," Women in the Caucasus, workshop 1, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 59: 8)
- "Working Together: Networking," Women in the Caucasus, Workshop 2 and 3, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 59: 9)
- Warsaw internship program, small grants, US study tour, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 59: 10)
- USIA-ECA, Women in the Caucasus (WIC 2), proposal, USIA-IDEE grant agreement and correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 60: 1)
- IDEE final report, USIA-IDEE correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 60: 2)
- NGO partner agreements, Training of Trainers/SDL workshop, general, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 60: 3)
- SDL Azerbaijan, Georgia, Armenia, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 60: 4)
- Small grants program, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 60: 5)
- Exchange program, Training of Trainers (TOT), NGO Assembly in Batumi, Georgia; TOT-US program; TOT English-language materials; correspondence: FED (TOT program), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 60: 6)
- Department of State, Education and Cultural Affairs (ECA), Women in the Caucasus (WIC 3), proposal and grant agreement with correspondence, 2002 (Box-folder 61: 1)
- Unfunded grant extension, drawdowns, 2002 (Box-folder 61: 2)
- IDEE interim and final reports, 2002 (Box-folder 61: 3)
- Cross-Border Forums materials, study tour materials, advanced Training of Trainers (TOT), 2002 (Box-folder 61: 4)
- Department of State, Education and Cultural Affairs (ECA), Women in the Caucasus (WIC 3), training manuals, Inam Workshop, grant partners agreements, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 62: 1)
- U.S. study tour, training for Caucasus NGO leaders, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 62: 2)
- WIC 3 newsletter, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 62: 3)
- Small grants program, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 62: 4)
- Small grants applications, Civic Forum, Batumi, WIC/WICA reconciliation, WIC/WICA descriptions, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 62: 5)
- Photographic prints of workshops, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 62: 6)
- Department of State, Education and Cultural Affairs (ECA), Women Networking in Central Asia (WICA 1), 2001-2002 (Box-folder 63: 1)
- Interim and final reports/reconciliation, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 63: 2)
- IDEE subgrant agreement, correspondence with Tashkent Public Education Center, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 63: 3)
- Women Networking in Central Asia Workshop documents, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 63: 4)
- U.S. study tour, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 63: 5)
- WICA small grants program (1), 2001-2002 (Box-folder 63: 6)
- WICA small grants program (2), 2001-2002 (Box-folder 64: 1)
- WICA small grants program (3), 2001-2002 (Box-folder 64: 2)
- WIC/WICA reconciliation and evaluation, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 64: 3)
- Department of State, Education and Cultural Affairs (ECA), tourism and community development in Ukraine, IDEE interim and final narrative reports, working files, U.S. study tour 1, Workshop 1, U.S. study tour preparation materials 1 and 2, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 65: 1)
- Department of State, Education and Cultural Affairs (ECA), Armenia, Building Community Connections, grant agreement, proposal and correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 66: 1)
- Financial report, Armenia and Ukraine, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 66: 2)
- Disbursement vouchers, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 66: 3)
- IDEE interim report, Armenia program, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 66: 4)
- Armenia program, final report, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 66: 5)
- Helsinki Citizens' Assembly narrative reports, accounting, project materials, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 66: 6)
- ECA, Armenia, Building Community Connections, assorted workshop materials, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 67: 1)
- Training of Trainers workshop, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 67: 2)
- Trip report, TOT 2nd workshop, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 67: 3)
- U.S. study tour, planning and evaluation, Citizens' Forum handbook, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 67: 4)
- Development Associates subcontract, Elections and Political Processes Project (EP3) in Ukraine, grant agreement/correspondence, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 68: 1)
- Work plan, NGO training series, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 68: 2)
- Chronological file (correspondence, etc.), 2001-2003 (Box-folder 68: 3)
- IDEE subcontract, election conferences, Lviv and Donetsk, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 68: 4)
- Activity reports and monthly charges, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 68: 5)
- Department of State, DRL (Bureau of Human Rights, Labor and Democracy), "Human Rights and Democratization Initiatives in Central Asia," grant agreement/proposal, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 69: 1)
- Financial reporting (Form PSC 272), 2003-2005 (Box-folder 69: 2)
- Quarterly reports 1-4, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 69: 3)
- 4th quarterly report materials, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 69: 4)
- IDEE final report, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 69: 5)
- Financial reports to DRL, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 69: 6)
- Grantee/workshop reports, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 69: 7)
- Department of State, DRL (Bureau of Human Rights, Labor and Democracy), "Human Rights and Democratization Initiatives in Central Asia," program reports, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 70: 1)
- Small grants reports, Kyrgystan, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 70: 2)
- Civic Forum reports, Kyrgystan, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 70: 3)
- Civic Forum reports, Tajikistan, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 70: 4)
- Centrum Asia Forum, Baku meeting, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 70: 5)
- Small grants program, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 70: 6)
- CLOSED (Boxes 71-73)
- Department of State, DRL, "Human Rights and Democracy Initiatives in Cuba Program," Cuba 2007, grant memos/grant agreements and amendments, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 74: 1)
- IDEE financial reports (DRL short form), 2005-2007 (Box-folder 74: 2)
- IDEE narrative reports 1-5, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 74: 3)
- IDEE narrative reports 6-7 (final), 2005-2007 (Box-folder 74: 4)
- Cuba Advisory Committee meeting No. 3, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 74: 5)
- Democracy for Cuba web site, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 74: 6)
- DemocracyforCuba.org, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 74: 7)
  Sample posted articles translated.
- Examples of IDEE training materials, 1992-2003 (Box-folder 74: 8)
- Department of State, DRL, "Human Rights and Democracy Initiatives in Cuba Program," Cuba 2007, background materials, organizations, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 75: 1)
- Background materials, Cuba trade unions, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 75: 2)
- Background materials, miscellaneous, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 75: 3)
- Background materials, GAO report on foreign assistance to Cuba, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 75: 4)
- Department of State, DRL, "Civil Society Direct Support in Cuba," grant memos/grant agreements and amendments, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 76: 1)
- Commerce Department, voluntary export of equipment/warning, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 76: 2)
- IDEE narrative reports 2-4, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 76: 3)
- IDEE narrative reports 5-10, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 76: 4)
- IDEE narrative reports (short and long forms), 2008-2009 (Box-folder 76: 5)
- IDEE financial reports (PSC 272 federal forms), 2008-2009 (Box-folder 76: 6)
- USAID, Cuba, annual program statement, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 76: 7)
- USAID, Cuba, political prisoners, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 76: 8)
- Cuba Chronicle of Events, English, Nos. 4-10, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 77: 1)
- Cuba Chronicle of Events, English, Nos. 11-20, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 77: 2)
- Cuba Chronicle of Events, English, Nos. 21-32, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 77: 3)
- Cuba Chronicle of Events, English, Nos. 33-65, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 77: 4)
- Publications, Analysis: Cuba, English, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 77: 5)
- Cuba Chronicle of Events, Spanish, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 77: 6)
- DVD disc: El Camino de Solidaridad, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 77: 7)
- Fidel Castro's Cuba, photojournal by Erazm Ciolek, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 78: 1)
  Published in Spanish, English, and Polish.
- Cuba in the Eyes of Children (two copies), 2005-2008 (Box-folder 78: 2)
- Pamphlets, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 78: 3)
- Pamphlets, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 78: 4)
- Demokracia 2 pamphlets, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 78: 5)
- Department of State DRL (Bureau of Human Rights, Labor and Democracy), grant programs, Cuba, pamphlets (2) published in Spanish, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 79: 1)
- Pamphlets, civil rights, Solidarity video, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 79: 2)
- Que est democracia y como debe ser ensenada en las escuelas? by Diane Ravitch, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 79: 3)
- Duplicate materials, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 79: 4)
- CLOSED (Boxes 80-87)
- Administrative files, accountant correspondence files, 1994-2010 (Box-folder 88: 1)
- 2001 audit files, 1994-2010 (Box-folder 88: 2)
- 2006, 2008, 2009 audit files, 1994-2010 (Box-folder 88: 3)
- USAID Clearinghouse reports, 1994-2010 (Box-folder 88: 4)
- Corporate records, IDEE and CSS Board of Director minutes/memos, 1994-2010 (Box-folder 88: 5)
- Board of Directors meetings (1997, 1998, 2001, 2004), 1994-2010 (Box-folder 88: 6)
- Board of Directors meetings (2007-2008, 2008-2009, April and October 2010), 1994-2010 (Box-folder 88: 7)
- Administrative files, DC registration and business license records, 1994-2010 (Box-folder 89: 1)
- Incorporation records, State of Delaware, 1994-2010 (Box-folder 89: 2)
- Original incorporation and IRS tax-exempt application records, 1994-2010 (Box-folder 89: 3)
- Negotiated Indirect Cost-Rate Agreement (NICRA), 1994-2010 (Box-folder 89: 4)
- Overhead rate calculations (Secker and Assoc.), indirect cost-rate proposals, 1994-2010 (Box-folder 89: 5)
- Accounting manual, 1994-2010 (Box-folder 89: 6)
- Administrative files, tax forms 1990 (return of tax-exempt organizations) (Box-folder 90: 1)
- Tax forms 1990 (return of tax-exempt organizations), 1994-2009 (Box-folder 90: 2)
- USAID PVO status registration, 1996-2003 (Box-folder 90: 3)
- USAID PVO status registration, original 1994 application (Box-folder 90: 4)
- Administrative files, audits, 1994-2010 (Box-folder 91: 1)
- Internet/domain registration (BooNet/Network Solutions), 1985-2010 (Box-folder 91: 2)
- Verizon records, 1985-2010 (Box-folder 91: 3)
- Office insurance records, 1985-2010 (Box-folder 91: 4)
- IDEE administrative files, personnel, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 92: 1)
- IDEE employment files, 1994-2004 (Box-folder 92: 2)
- Personnel files, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 92: 3)
- Personnel files, Tashpulatova, 1985-2010 (Box-folder 92: 4)
- Paycheck, 1985-2010 (Box-folder 92: 5)
- Office opening, office lease, 1994 June (Box-folder 92: 6)
- Ongoing financial reports, phone service: cellular, computers: Dell, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 92: 7)
- Donations to charity, Blue Cross/Blue Shield, federal employment forms (W-4s), 1985-2010 (Box-folder 92: 8)
- D.C., MD and VA employment forms, tax correspondence, 1985-2010 (Box-folder 92: 9)
- Unemployment claims, Civitas meeting in Prague, report of Voluntary Agencies (Voluntary Foreign Aid Programs), 2004 (Box-folder 92: 10)
- Publications, Fidel Castro's Cuba, Cuba in the Eyes of Children, Caucasus, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 93: 1)
- Publications, Uncaptive Minds, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 93: 2)
- Publications, Uncaptive Minds, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 94: 1)
- Publications, Centers for Pluralism, El ABC de la Democracia, 1999-2003 (Box-folder 94: 2)
- Publications, Centers for Pluralism, newsletter, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 94: 3)
- Publications, Uncaptive Minds, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 95: 1)
- Centers for Pluralism publications, newsletter, 1998-2003 (Box-folder 95: 2)
- Bookkeeping documents, 1987-1993 (Box-folder 96: 1)